eadgear.com 2012-10-16

# Privacy Policy - eAdGear - Web Design and SEO Company, Website Design, Website Design for Pleasanton, Dublin, Livermore, Danville, San Ramon, Tri-Valley, Walnut Creek, Concord, Fremont, San Leandro, Hayward, Castro Valley, Pleasant Hill, California,CA, East Bay

web design and seo company

### privacy policy

###### eAdGear PRIVACY POLICY

eAdGear strives to offer its website users the many advantages of downloadable software for purchase. Our eAdGear Tool Box of products is solely intended to help small and midsize companies grow their business and provide an interactive, user friendly experience. We may use Personally Identifiable Information (your name, e-mail address, street address, telephone number) subject to the terms of this privacy policy. We will never sell, barter, or rent your email address to any third party. 

###### How We Gather Information From Users

How we collect and store information depends on the website page you are visiting, the activities in which you elect to participate and the purchases made. For example, you may be asked to provide information when you register for access to certain portions of our website or request certain features when you make a purchase. Like most Websites, eAdGear also collects information automatically and through the use of electronic tools that may be transparent to our users. For example, we may log the name of your Internet Service Provider or use cookie technology to recognize you and hold information from your visit. Among other things, the cookies may store your eAdGear user name and password, sparing you from having to re-enter that information each time you visit. As eAdGear develops additional software, we may also gather R&D information through other means. In certain cases, you can choose not to provide us with information, for example by setting your browser to refuse to accept cookies, but if you do, you may be unable to access certain portions of the website or may be asked to re-enter your user name and password and we may not be able to customize eAdGear’s tool box of software packages according to your preferences.

###### What We Do With The Information We Collect

Like other software application providers, we collect information to enhance your user experience and deliver more individualized content and advertising. We respect your privacy and do not share your information with anyone.

Aggregated Information (information that does not personally identify you) may be used in many ways. For example, we may combine information about your usage patterns with similar information obtained from other users to help enhance our website and products offered (e.g., to learn which software tools viewed most or what features are most attractive to users). Aggregated Information may occasionally be shared in general terms with our advertisers and business partners. Again, this information does not include any Personally Identifiable Information about you or allow anyone to identify you individually.

We may use Personally Identifiable Information collected on eAdGear to communicate with you about your registration and customization preferences, offered by eAdGear and other topics we think you might find of interest.

Personally Identifiable Information collected by eAdGear may also be used for other purposes, including but not limited to website administration, troubleshooting, and other communications with you. Certain third parties who provide technical support for the operation of our website (our web host for example) may access such information. We will use your information only as permitted by law.

We may disclose your information in response to a court order, or at other times, when we believe we are reasonably required to do so by law. If we find a user not abiding by our eAdGear Terms and Conditions we reserve the right to contact the enforcement authorities whenever we deem it appropriate or necessary. Please note we may not provide you with notice prior to disclosure in such cases.

###### Affiliated Sites, Linked Sites and Advertisements

eAdGear expects its partners, advertisers and affiliates to respect the privacy of our users. Be aware, however, that third parties, including our partners, advertisers, affiliates and other content providers, may have their own privacy and data collection policies and practices. For example, during your visit to our website you may link to, or view as part of an eAdGear page frame certain content that is actually created or hosted by a third party. Also, through eAdGear you may be introduced to, or be able to access, information, Websites, features, offered by other parties. eAdGear is not responsible for the actions or policies of such third parties.

Other features available on our website may offer services operated by third parties and may use cookies or other technology to gather information. eAdGear does not control the use of this technology by third parties or the resulting information, and is not responsible for any actions or policies of such third parties.

You should also be aware that if you voluntarily disclose Personally Identifiable Information on message boards or in chat areas, that information can be viewed publicly and can be collected and used by third parties without our knowledge and may result in unsolicited messages from other individuals or third parties. Such activities are beyond the control of eAdGear and this policy.

###### Children

eAdGear does not knowingly collect or solicit Personally Identifiable Information from or about children under 13 except as permitted by law. If we discover we have received any information from a child under 13 in violation of this policy, we will delete that information immediately. If you believe eAdGear has any information from or about anyone under 13, please email us at: Compliance.Dept@eAdGear.com.

eAdGear reserves the right to change this policy at any time. Please check this page periodically for changes. Your continued use of our website following the posting of changes to these terms will mean you accept those changes. Information collected prior to the time any change is posted will be used according to the rules and laws that applied at the time the information was collected.

###### Governing Law

This policy and the use of this website are governed by the judiciary Government's law in the State of California. If a dispute arises under this Policy we agree to first try to resolve it with the help of a mutually agreed-upon mediator in the judiciary Government. Any costs and fees other than attorney fees associated with the mediation will be shared equally by each of us.

If it proves impossible to arrive at a mutually satisfactory solution through mediation, we agree to submit the dispute to binding arbitration in the said; judiciary Government, under the rules of the American Arbitration Association. Judgment upon the award rendered by the arbitration may be entered in any court with jurisdiction to do so.

eAdGear is controlled, operated and administered entirely in the judiciary Government within the State of California. This statement and the policies outlined herein are not intended to and do not create any contractual or other legal rights in or on behalf of any party. 

support@eadgear.com
